My grandpa was generous and charitable.
He saved lives asking nothing in return.
Benefactor Li,
you killed your savior with your own hands.
You're going to hell.
Madam,
don't listen to their nonsense.
They sneaked into our home
- just for the money! - Shut up!
As to who's talking nonsense,
I can judge for myself.
Those who accidentally killed the wives
and Mengzhu are Chunmei and her siblings.
However, their motive for murder
wasn't for money at all.
That's right.
My siblings and I infiltrated the Li household
just to
seek justice for Elder Ding and Xiao Bao.
You're talking nonsense!
To repay Elder Ding for saving my life,
I built a bridge for their family.
But the river was deep and fast,
so the bridge just wouldn't hold.
You're insane! You're a monster!
You tied Xiao Bao up as a Sacrifice to the River God,
for a human foundation sacrifice!
Madam, you see...
You must stand up for me!
Just stay out of this!
What did you say happened to Xiao Bao?
Benefactor Li
drowned Elder Ding and Xiao Bao for a human foundation sacrifice.
Let me go!
Grandpa!
You bandits!
Help me!
Behave!
Grandpa!
Let me go!
You bandits!
Grandpa!
Help me, Grandpa!
You prefer the hard way!
Once you two are dead,
this land will be mine.
Do it!
Help me, Grandpa!
Offer them both as a Sacrifice to the River God!
A human foundation sacrifice! A Sacrifice to the River God!
Heaven and Earth, hear my plea,
Lord Lao, show your divinity!
Help me, Grandpa!
Elder Ding!
Xiao Bao! Xiao Bao!
Elder Ding! Xiao Bao!
Xiao Bao!
Inspector Mu
Benefactor Li is the real murderer.
We sneaked into the Li residence
just to assassinate him alone.
We never meant to mistakenly kill the wives and the young lady.
Wait.
You mean
Elder Ding and Xiao Bao
were both killed by him?
Then why didn't the police arrest him?
Right, exactly.
Brilliant, Madam.
You, shut up.
Spot on.
Master.
The grandfather and grandson who lived here,
could they be the two you saw in your hallucination?
Put under a bridge as a human foundation sacrifice,
their spirits won't rest.
This female inspector
and her dad are birds of a feather.
They've both been bought off by Benefactor Li.
We should just kill them all
to avenge Elder Ding and Xiao Bao.
Boss.
The boss is right.
This female inspector protects scumbags.
She's no good either.
Listen to me.
It's my fault for being soft-hearted.
I thought this female inspector would uphold the law.
Who knew
she'd only investigate us for accidentally killing
the wives and the young lady,
completely ignoring Benefactor Li killing them for their house.
I'm going to ask you today,
we hinted to you multiple times
to investigate Elder Ding and Xiao Bao's case.
Why did you turn a blind eye?
Chief!
I want to report a crime!
I saw it with my own eyes.
Elder Ding and Xiao Bao were murdered by Benefactor Li!
Enough.
We've already investigated this.
Elder Ding and his grandson were fishing,
slipped into the water,
and due to poor swimming skills,
accidentally drowned.
Stop making up lies here!
Elder Ding and Xiao Bao didn't slip into the water.
It was Benefactor Li.
He wanted to seize Elder Ding's land,
so he sank them to the bottom of the river to drown!
Right.
You're saying Benefactor Li
wanted to seize Elder Ding's land?
Benefactor Li would have to be out of his mind
to want Elder Ding's worthless plot of land
and run-down house.
If you ask me,
you're the one who's out of your mind.
Men!
- Take her out. - It really was Li
who killed Elder Ding and Xiao Bao!
- Investigate it again! - Move.
- Keep moving. - Chief!
Chief!
Keep moving.
I don't have the spare time
to investigate how some wretched old man died.
I heard Master Li say
that this gold ingot
is an antique from the Yuncang Kingdom.
Your father took bribes from Benefactor Li.
He and Benefactor Li are birds of a feather.
No, don't get this wrong.
My father is my father,
and I am me.
I have no ties to Benefactor Li whatsoever.
If my father doesn't solve this case today,
I will definitely take over.
As long as I'm in Lijia Town,
there will be no unjust or false cases.
Madam.
- Shut up. - You... you...
You keep talking.
Just when we had nowhere to seek justice,
we happened to see the Li residence was hiring.
Good.
Next.
Hiring!
The Li residence is hiring!
Okay.
Alright, next.
Zhang Yong.
Okay.
- Next. - Thank you.
My name is Liu Wei.
Okay.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Mister, I can do needlework.
Needlework?
Needlework.
And what about these two?
He can do carpentry.
I do carpentry,
and I'm good at carving.
Look, I made this.
Nice.
As for me...
- His younger brother. - We're a trio. A trio.
I can...
I can do flower arranging.
Flower arranging?
Yes.
Flower arranging.
Good, alright.
I'll take all three of you then.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
So we siblings sneaked into the Li residence,
and began our plan to assassinate Benefactor Li.
These round holes through the walls,
when the wind blows through them,
create resonance,
producing these strange sounds.
This Desert Rose,
both in appearance and smell,
is very similar to Oleander.
The killer used the Oleander from the garden
to replace the Desert Rose.
The First Madam drank the highly toxic Oleander
and was poisoned to death.
Madam! Madam!
What made the garden's flowers wither
is the Caustic soda in this soil.
This dressing table
should have been further inside,
but was dragged here.
To execute this plan precisely, the killer
even tampered with the hemp rope in advance.
At 1:00 PM,
they focused the magnifying glass's light
onto the chandelier's hemp rope,
burning it until it snapped.
The flower demon killed someone!
This water intake valve
was newly built.
Someone modified the water valve.
I promised him
that after singing "Cinnabar Well",
I would go with him to Cuixiang Pavilion for dinner.
Someone purposely drew Miasma into the Li residence,
turning it into a murder weapon.
This was originally Master Li's bedroom.
This wooden puppet
has been rigged with hidden weapons.
So the killer's target
must have been Master Li.
Chunmei
This puppet
was Xiao Bao's toy.
Every time it appeared beside the victims,
you must have put it there, right?
That's right.
I just wanted to remind Benefactor Li
that someone would avenge Elder Ding and Xiao Bao.
But in taking revenge for them,
you killed many innocent people.
How are you any different from murderers?
We only wanted to kill Benefactor Li.
But he luckily escaped every time.
We never thought
we'd accidentally kill the wives and young lady.
Just when we were at our wits' end,
the three sisters returned.
We listened to Grandpa
and stayed in the provincial capital,
going to school and learning acrobatics.
But when we finally returned to Lijia Town,
Grandpa was already gone.
Why did Grandpa's thatched cottage
turn into a big mansion?
Coming! Coming!
Sister Chunmei,
where is Grandpa?
Come inside first.
We siblings hid in the Li household,
plotting to kill Benefactor Li,
solely to avenge Elder Ding and Xiao Bao.
But that Benefactor Li,
as if he had an expert helping him,
dodged death at critical moments every time.
That's why we kept failing.
I regret it so much every single day.
The three wives treated me with such kindness.
Because of our negligence,
they died innocent and tragic deaths.
I am truly unforgivable.
It's my fault for lacking skill,
and accidentally killing the three wives.
At the temple,
I lit ever-burning lamps for the wives.
I hope they can rest in peace soon.
But what good does that do?
We caused all of this.
We deserve to die a thousand deaths.
Since we tried everything
and still couldn't kill Benefactor Li,
then we'll torture him every day,
to make his life a living hell.
We sisters
learned great skills at the acrobatics troupe.
We can definitely handle him.
I can do disguises.
I can sing opera.
I have a plan.
Hurry!
This is the truth behind the haunting at Li Manor.
The six of us worked together
just to punish
the true culprit who murdered Elder Ding and his grandson.
Stop slandering me!
You claim I hurt Elder Ding and his grandson?
Then tell me this.
He was just a penniless old man.
Why would I bother harming him?